

ADESH KUMAR



CONTACT

- Adeshgangwar1996@gmai I.com
- + 91 8979988766
- 181/f2 Shalimar Garden Extn. 1, Ghaziabad India 201005

SKILLS

- Expertise of HTML DOM and frontend JavaScript according to ES6 specifications.
- Experience with CI/CD tools such as Jenkins.
- Willingness to share knowledge and continue learning.
- Best practices and standards.
- Passion for quality, good design and clean code.
- Testing and deployment .
- Experience in working with REST APIs and ISON.
- Experience with common frontend development tools such as Babel, Webpack, NPM, etc.
- Work with agile methodologies (Scrum).
- Experience with version control (Git & GitHub).
- Experience with Responsive Web Design.

SUMMARY

Versatile software engineer who works well both as part of a team and independently. Strong organizational skills coupled with more than 4+ years of expertise. Highly educated with the capability to deliver on key project milestones. Seeking to secure an engineering role with an internationally astute firm involved in the Software industry. Seeking the chance to architect new software applications.

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER -UI

08.2019-Current

BOLD Technology System Pvt. Ltd, Noida

- Creating and managing all UI stuff for International Portals.
- Responsible to create reusable components that can be used in other product as well.
- Conducting ABTests, Tracking and other stuff for all LiveCareer International.
- Managing Brand Guidelines and single code base for all portals.
- Ensure cross browser and cross platform compatibility.
- Familiar with creating and managing large application code structure.

UI DEVELOPER

01.2019-08.2019

RNM E-Services Pvt. Ltd (iChamp India), Gurugram

- Implemented and tested enhancement feature requests to improve product functionality and extend performance.
- Modified existing software systems to enhance performance and add new features.
- Modified existing iChamp application to correct coding errors, upgrade interfaces and improve overall performance.
- Ensured that product adhered to brand guidelines.

WEB DESIGNER

Technohills Web Pvt. Ltd, Rohtak

05.2017-12.2018

EDUCATION

07.2014 -06.2018 Bachelor of Technology: Computer Science & Engineering

HOBBIES /INTEREST

- Travelling.
- Listening old songs.
- $\textbf{PUNJAB TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY, PUNJAB}_{Reviewed \ information \ regularly \ on \ websites \ and \ pages \ to }$ ensure that it was accurate.
 - Ensured that sites adhered to brand guidelines.
 - Created web materials to be used in marketing and email campaigns.
 - Validated code for proper structuring, security and compatibility with different browsers, devices or operating
 - Redesigned sites to enhance navigation and improve visual appeal.

- Designed, built and maintained complete websites.
- Determined job priorities for multiple projects and communicated them with the entire team.

CORE SKILLS

- Primary Skills:
 JavaScript | React/Redux | SASS | Node.js | HTML | CSS |
 Angular
- Secondary Skills:
 Ionic | jQuery | D3.js | Bootstrap | Flexbox Layout | Express |
 MongoDB | REST | Webpack | Firebase | Photoshop